{
    "subject": "resource/Claude_Crowl",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Turkey",
    "human_readable": "Claude Crowl died in Turkey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9023919105529785,
            "question": "Is there information available about Claude Crowl's life before his death in Turkey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8962730169296265,
            "question": "What might have led Claude Crowl to be in Turkey at the time of his death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8149974942207336,
            "question": "Where did Claude Crowl die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7567568421363831,
            "question": "What country was Claude Crowl in when he died?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5313680171966553,
            "question": "Were there any notable events or circumstances surrounding Claude Crowl's time in Turkey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4829098582267761,
            "question": "Are there any historical events or contexts that could be relevant to Claude Crowl's presence in Turkey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4789808392524719,
            "question": "Did Claude Crowl have any family or connections in Turkey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27873343229293823,
            "question": "Are there any records or sources that offer further insights into Claude Crowl's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23667371273040771,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about Claude Crowl's background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23151732981204987,
            "question": "Was Claude Crowl known for any particular profession or accomplishments?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Claude Crowl died in Turkey.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2981_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more details about Claude Crowl's background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2981_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any records or sources that offer further insights into Claude Crowl's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2981_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Claude Crowl have any family or connections in Turkey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2981_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2981_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2981_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2981_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2981_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2981_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2981_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2981_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2981_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2981_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2981_46.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Claude Crowl died in Turkey.\" Specifically, they mention his death at Gallipoli on 25th April 1915, which is located in modern-day Turkey."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}